[{"id": 1401, "question": "Spring is here and so is the cycling season. Here are some tips on how to do it safely and comfortably. Watch your feet--Pushing with the wrong part of the foot can raise your risk of developing a painful injury of the heel and arch , says Rob Werstine, a sports physiotherapist and board member of the Canadian Physiotherapy Association. You should push with the ball of your foot, he says. Layer up--While it's still cool, wear layers of clothing, with clothing close to the body that breathes and outer layers that do not absorb water. Go for bright colors that increase your visibility . Be reasonable--If you are just starting out and aren't in good shape, don't sign up for a 50-kilometre ride. And while cycling is great exercise for people who want to get into shape, if your doctor advises y...\n\nQ: Which part of the foot should one use when cycling?", "options": ["The heel.", "The arch.", "The ball.", "The toes."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2022, "question": ". Passage 1 Every morning, when we wake up, we have 24 brand-new hours to live. What a gift! We have the capacity to live in a way that these 24 hours will bring peace, joy, and happiness to ourselves and to others. Peace is right here and now, in ourselves and in everything we do and see. The question is whether or not we are in touch with it. We don't have to travel far away to enjoy the blue sky. We don't have to leave our city or even our neighborhood to enjoy the eyes of a beautiful child. Even the air we breathe can be a source of joy. We can smile, breathe, walk, and eat our meals in a way that allows us to be in touch with the abundance of happiness that is available. We are very good at preparing how to live, but not very good at living. We know how to sacrifice ten years for a di...\n\nQ: In Passage 1 line 11, the list (\"a job...house\") presents things that most people    _   .", "options": ["assume they will eventually obtain", "eventually realize are overrated", "are unwilling to make sacrifices for", "see as worth much effort to acquire"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 203, "question": "Reading can be a social activity. Think of the people who belong to book groups. They choose books to read and then meet m discuss them. Now, the website BookCrossing.com rums the page on the traditional idea of a book group. Members go on the site and register books they own that they would like.sham. BookCrossing provides an identifying numb\" .stick inside the book. Then the person 'releases' the book by leaving it in a public place. The hope is that the book will have an adventure, traveling far and wide with each new reader who finds it. Bruce Pederson is the chief executive of BookCrossing. He and his wife Hearer started the site with Ron Hombaker in 2001. Mr. Pederson says, \"One of the founding principles was the two things that change your life: tha people you meet and the books you...\n\nQ: The passage is mast probably written to  _  .", "options": ["attract more people to join BookCrossing", "encourage readers m surf the insurer", "introduce a new style of reading and sharing", "describe how BookCrossing was set up"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1802, "question": "Every one of us gets so used to punctuation marks that not many of us give them a secondthought.Actually,the ancient Greeks wrote this way.The lack of punctuation marks probably didn't bother good readers,though.As they read,they just put pauses where they fit best. Also at this time,sentences switched directions.A sentence read from leftto right.The next one read right to left,and then left to right again,etc.The ancient Romans sometimes punctuatedlike this:They put somethingthat can separate words in a sentence.The wordpunctuationactually comes from this idea andthe Latin word\"punctum\"which means a lot. When the 5th century arrived,there were just twopunctuation marks:spaces and points.The spaces separated words while the points showed pauses in reading.Then in the 13th century,a printer...\n\nQ: We can learn from the passage that  _  .", "options": ["ancient Romans didn't use any punctuation marks", "exclamation and question marks came from Latin", "spaces and slashes were already used before the 5th century", "Aldus Manutiusfast started to use commas"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2836, "question": "In the late 1960's, many people in North America turned their attention to environmental problems, and new steel-and-glass skyscrapers were widely criticized. Ecologists pointed out that a forest of tall buildings in a city often overburdens public transportation and parking lots. Skyscrapers are also consumers and wasters of electric power. In one recent year, the addition of 17 million square feet of skyscrapers office space in New York City raised the peak daily demand for electricity by 120,000 kilowatts--enough to supply the entire city of Albany, prefix = st1 /New York, for a day. Glass-walled skyscrapers can be especially wasteful. The heat loss ( or gain) through a wall of half-inch plate glass is more than ten times that through a typical brick wall filled with insulation board. T...\n\nQ: According to the passage, what is one disadvantage of skyscrapers that have mirrored walls?", "options": ["The surrounding air is heated.", "Construction time is increased.", "The windows must be cleaned daily.", "Extra air-conditioning equipment is needed."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1534, "question": "Postcards to myself In 50 years of traveling Colin McCorpuodale has visited every country in the world, except three.And everywhere he goes,he sends himself a postcard.He always chooses a postcard with a beautiful view,and sticks on an interesting stamp.Usually he writes just a short message to himself.His latest one,from the Malians island,read Good fishing. On a wall in his home in London there is a large map of the world.There are hundreds of little red pins stuck in it.\"It's good to get a pin in the map,\" says Mr.McCorquodale, \"but I follow the rules.I'm allowed to stick one in only if I've been in a place for more than 24 hours.\" Naturally,Mr.McCorpuodale has his favorite places.New Zealand he describes as\"wonderful\".In Europe,he says,\"Italy is a favorite place.But in Italy tourists a...\n\nQ: Tourists in Italy are often    _  .", "options": ["beaten", "helped", "encouraged", "cheated"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3226, "question": "\"For those who haven't been to Tibet is a dream; for those who have already been there, Tibet is a memory.\" said Li Wan, a graduate from Zhongshan University. \"For me, living there is my dream and happiness.\" Li was suddenly crazy about Tibet after working there for three months as an office clerk. Since 2008, Li has spent most of her time travelling in Tibet. Four years have passed and she has been almost every corner of Tibet. Li came to Tibet firstly because of her desire for personal freedom. She entered Tibet along the Yunnan-Tibetan road, enjoying the special view happily. She was surprised to find that it is a white paradise on earth. Although she couldn't even speak a word of Tibetan language, she had no difficulty in communicating with natives. \"To me, they are free, generous, sim...\n\nQ: What can we infer from the passage?", "options": ["Li Wan felt it hard to communicate with natives because of their special culture.", "Li Wan couldn't live in Tibet well because she had little money to travel.", "Li Wan survived many difficulties but she still insisted on her dream.", "Li Wan fell in love with Tibet after she made tours there."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1392, "question": "In the market of luxury brands, Chinese consumers are only second to the Japanese in the world. Across the globe it's clear that the young generation are increasingly relying on expensive brands for their self-image. Personally I am a fashion-lover, at least in spirit. I love to look at clothes and shoes. But I don't understand why people spend large amounts of money on designer labels. Certainly, young people, whether in China or elsewhere, should be building their self-confidence in other ways. When a young woman shows off a handbag worth two months' salary, that's a scary thing. What are the psychological factors forcing young people to take on debt for designer items? The desire to say, \"Hey, look at me. I'm wealthy. I have social status.\" Scientists have found the acquisition of luxur...\n\nQ: The author believes that young people would borrow money for luxury brands psychologically to   _  .", "options": ["show off", "improve appearance", "build up confidence", "make others jealous"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3422, "question": "Hello-Hello, a creative mobile language learning company, announced the launch of Hello-Hello World, a free application for the iPad that helps people learn a new language by connecting them with native speakers through social networking. The application lets users complete language lessons and connect with Hello-Hello's global community of language learners with members in almost 100 countries to help each other in the learning process. Hello-Hello World is available in 11 different languages and allows users to submit both oral and writing exercises for their friends and Hello-Hello's language experts to review. Users are also able to provide written feedback on their friend's exercises directly from their mobile devices. \"The most effective way to learn a new language is through total i...\n\nQ: What does Sarah Gontijo think it takes to learn a new language effectively?", "options": ["Hard work and practice.", "Cultural understanding.", "A language learning environment.", "Modern mobile technology."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2624, "question": "The story of Juno and Lucas is one of the most touching stories about the amazing relationship between humans and their companion animals. Juno is a Belgian Malinois . The dog was beautiful but was given up by its owners, as they did not want to take on the responsibility. Lucas, a little boy, had a strange illness, a condition that stops the body's ability to process enzymes .As his life continues, he will lose the ability to speak and his physical and mental abilities will degrade till he is left in a vegetative state. The average life expectancy for the patients is 15 years. Chester, the boy's father, wanted his child to enjoy his life on earth as much as possible and looked into getting a service dog for the child. However, Lucas wasn't a good candidate due to his deteriorating abiliti...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is NOT true?", "options": ["The author has also adopted a dog and loves it.", "Juno has gained some skills accompanying Lucas.", "Chester was very satisfied with Juno's performances.", "Lucas recovered from the disease accompanied by Juno."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1371, "question": "\"Make-A-Wish\" is one of the world's most well-known charities . It makes wishes come true for childrenwho have serious illnesses. It gives them hope and joy and helps them forget about their health problems and have fun. It all started in 1980 in Phoenix, Arizona. Christopher was a 7-year-old boy who was very sick. He always dreamed ofbecoming a police officer. Tommy Austin and Ron Cox, two police officers, made his wish come true. They gaveChristopher a tour of the city in a police helicopter and made a real police uniform for him. There are four kinds of wishes children usually have: I wish to go. Children usually want to travel or go to a concert, a game or a park. I wish to meet. Children sometimes want to meet their favourite actors, singers or players. I wish to be. Some children wis...\n\nQ: Which kind of wishes does Christopher have?", "options": ["I wish to go.", "I wish to meet.", "I wish to be.", "I wish to have."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1885, "question": "Teen Dating can be fun if you are aware of its pros and cons and are also aware of the ways to protect yourself. There are a couple of suggestions you would like to know before you are out for dating. Do not go out for dating with somebody whom you have seen only a few times and does not know much about him or her. Before leaving on a date, know the exact plans for the evening and make sure a parent or friend knows these plans and what time to expect you home. Let your date know that you are expected to call or tell that person when you get in. Similarly, if you leave a party with someone you do not know well, make sure you tell another person you are leaving and with whom. Ask a friend to call and make sure you arrive home safely. No matter how good the person appears to you, trust your i...\n\nQ: Which of the following is forbidden when dating according to the passage?", "options": ["Going out for dating with a stranger.", "Knowing the plan for the evening.", "Telling your parents about the date.", "Telling the person you date that your parents know about the date."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2634, "question": "I took the bus to work for many years. No one knew each other; the passengers all sat there sleepily in the morning. The bus was cheerless and silent. One of the passengers was a small gray-haired man who took the bus to the center for senior citizens every morning. No one ever paid very much attention to him. One July morning he said good morning to the driver and smiled. The driver nodded guardedly . The rest of us were silent. The next day, the old man boarded with a big smile and said in a loud voice: \"A very good morning to you all!\" Some of us looked up, amazed, and murmured \"Good Morning\" in reply. The following weeks, our friend was dressed in a nice old suit and tie. His thin hair had been carefully combed. He said good morning to us every day and we gradually began to nod and tal...\n\nQ: From the passage, we can infer that  _", "options": ["people always cared about each other on the bus", "people were unhappy and sleepy on the bus because they were tired", "smiles can shorten the distance between people", "people are not good at communicating in the country"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2191, "question": "Recently a committee of the National Academy of Sciences inprefix = st1 /Washingtonreleased a report .It confirmed that world temperatures increased about six-tenths of a degree Celsius in the last one hundred years. The report also confirmed evidence that the level of carbon dioxide in increasing. The best information about climate in the past comes from tests of ice many kilometers deep in Antarctica and Greenland .These tests show that levels of carbon dioxide today are the highest ever measured .These findings have led scientists to believe that carbon dioxide is a major cause of climate warming. Carbon dioxide is released into the atmosphere when fuel is burned. Oil ,coal and wood are all fuels that release the gas .When biological waste breaks down ,it also releases carbon dioxide. H...\n\nQ: Those studies carried out in North Carolinasuggest that_.", "options": ["more carbon dioxide is beneficial for trees' growth for many decades", "trees' function for absorbing carbon dioxide is limited", "carbon dioxide is the main cause for global warming", "leaves falling from trees can send out more oxygen"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1050, "question": "California places limits on water use to deal with the state's four-year drought. Californians are feeling the heat after Governor Jerry Brown announced an order that puts mandatory statewide water cutbacks into effect. California has faced water-use cutbacks in the past. In January 2014, Governor Brown called for residents to curb their water use by 20 percent, but many places around the state failed to meet that goal. This most recent announcement, however, marks the first time in the state's history that mandatory restrictions have been ordered. Most of California's water supply comes from the Sierra Nevada mountain range snowpack. Normally, during the spring and summer, this snow melts and puts new supplies into groundwater. but this past winter, the snowpack reached its lowest point s...\n\nQ: This year's drought in California is mainly caused by_.", "options": ["The lack of rainfall last winter.", "Its residents' excessive water use.", "The historically low temperature last winter.", "The reduction of snowpack on the Sierra Nevada"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1034, "question": "I was now in my twenty third year of residence in this island and was accustomed to the place and to the manner of living. If it had not been the savages who had come to the place to disturb me, I could have been content to spent the rest of my time there, even to the last moment, till I had laid me down and died, like the old goat in the cave. I had also arrived to some little recreations and amusements, which made the time pass more pleasantly with me a great deal than it did before. At first, I had taught my Poll to speak. And he did it so familiarly and talked so clearly and plain that it was very pleasant to me. And he lived with me no less than twenty six years. How long he might live afterwards, I don't know; though I know they have an idea in Brazil that they live a hundred years. ...\n\nQ: How many parrots did Robin Crusoe mention in this passage?", "options": ["2", "3", "4", "5"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 763, "question": "We've all heard the phrase \"love is patient\", but one couple in prefix = st1 /Michigan, took this phrase to a whole new level. On Monday, February 13, Willard Mason sat down to talk about his relationship with the love he lost more than 60 years ago. Good fortune and fate recently helped the couple reunite. In 1941, Willard Mason and Llah Ost, both senior 2 students, became engaged to be married and began planning their lives together. But Willard moved away to work at Willow Run Bomber Plant, where he met and fell in love with a woman named Helvi. He broke off his long distance engagement to Llah and married Helvi in 1942. Llah later found love with someone else. Both had happy marriages and raised families. Then, in 2003, Helvi died. A year later, Willard found himself back in his hometo...\n\nQ: Which of the following should be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["A Car Accident Brought about Reunion", "Second Marriage and Second Happiness", "No Argument in a Reunited Family", "Reunited after 62 Years."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1469, "question": "New rules and behavior standards for the middle school students came out in March. Middle school is going to use a new way to decide who the top students are. The best students won't only have high marks. They will also be kids who don't dye their hair, smoke or drink. The following are some of the new rules. Tell the truth. Have you ever copied others' work in an exam? Don't do it again if you did it before! That's not something an honest student should do. If you have played computer games for two hours in your room, don't tell your parents you have done your homework. Do more at school. Good students love animals and care for other people. April is a bird-loving month in China. Did your school do anything to celebrate? If so, you should join it! In this way, you can learn more about ani...\n\nQ: The passage tells us how to   _  .", "options": ["be top students", "do more at school", "care for others", "use the Internet"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 931, "question": "Talk about a real-life hero! Ten-year-old Larry Champagne from St. Louis, Missouri, hit the brake on a runaway school bus. He saved himself and 20 other kids on board from disaster. It all happened in one terrible accident. On the way to school, the bus driver, Ernestine Blackman, suddenly fell ill. Seeing the car was running away, the other kids started to scream, but Larry ran to the front and stopped the bus. \"At first I thought, 'We're going to die,'\" says Larry, \"but after I pressed the brake, I felt safe.\" Larry's speedy reaction made news all over the country. He appeared on TV shows as a hero. The bus company gave Larry a big gift. His school hung a medal of honor around his neck. \"My grandmother always tells me to do what's right,\" says Larry. He thanked his brother, Jerrick, 9, w...\n\nQ: What did Larry do to save the runaway bus?", "options": ["He parked it for the sleeping bus driver.", "He helped all the kids climb out through the windows.", "He made a call to the police.", "He pressed the brake."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1958, "question": "In today's throw away society, dealing with the city's growing mountain of waste is an inereasing challenge for the city countil . Recently. Edinburgh is faced with the problem of dssposing of about250,000 Million tons of waster a year . Despite different ways to dispose of much of it in a green manner---largely through encouraging tecycling---its aging facilities such as the Powderhall landfill do not have the ability to deal with it. The European Union(EU) has issued a new policy, regulating how such mountains of waster are to hr disposed of. The five councils (Edinburgh. East Lothian. West Lothian. Midlethian and Borders) face fine around $18million a year from 2013 it they don't inerease recycling levels and rely less on landfill. With this in mind, the coumlls got together with the id...\n\nQ: The city council of Edinburgh rejected the suggestion to open a huge landfill site near Portobello because     .", "options": ["a name from a private company", "the comelier was not interested in it", "it was not supports by EU", "the local poodle was waist it"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 386, "question": "A meteor that exploded over Russia's Ural mountains and sent burning to earth has set off a rush to find fragments of the space rock which hunters hope could fetch thousands of dollars a piece. Friday's explosion and following shockwave shattered windows, injured almost 1200 people and caused about $33 million worth of damage, said local authorities. It also started a \"meteorite rush\" around the industrial city of Chelyabinsk,where groups of people have started _ the snow and ice. \"The price is hard to say yet... The fewer meteorites that are discovered, the higher their price is.\" Said Dmitry Kachkalin, a member of the Russian Society of Amateur Meteorite Lovers. Meteorites are parts of a meteor that have fallen to earth. Scientists at the Urals Federal University were the first to announ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, lots of people rushed to find meteorites for  _  .", "options": ["fun", "money", "research", "fame"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3381, "question": "Tayka Hotel De Sal Where: Tahua, Bolivia How much: About $95 a night Why it's cool: You've stayed at hotels made of brick or wood, but salt? That's something few can claim. Tayka Hotel de Sal is made totally of salt -- including the beds (though you'll sleep on regular mattresses and blankets). The hotel sits on the Salar de Uyuni, a prehistoric dried-up lake that's the world's biggest salt flat. Builders use the salt from the 4,633-square-mile flat to make the bricks, and glue them together with a paste of wet salt that hardens when it dries. When rain starts to dissolve the hotel, the owners just mix up more salt paste to strengthen the bricks. Green Magic Nature Resort Where: Vythiri, India How much: About $240 a night Why it's cool: Riding a pulley -operated lift 86 feet to your treeto...\n\nQ: Which of the following about Tayka Hotel de Sal is true?", "options": ["The hotel is the cheapest among the four mentioned.", "Everything in the hotel is made of salt.", "The glue can prevent the rain from dissolving the hotel.", "It is located on a prehistoric dried-up lake."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2069, "question": "The Internet has become a part of our everyday life and there is nothing we can do without it.It is a means of communication as well as a good way of relieving and having fun.No matter in what place of the world,the Internet is the same for every one of us. If we hope to improve our knowledge or look for a certain piece of information, the Internet is the perfect tool for our need.If we do not have the time to shop, ordering online is the solution to our problem.The Internet is very useful to most people. There is no doubt that the Internet also has some bad points.I'm speaking about the harmful information,which may come up in the most unexpected paces.You can sometimes come across violence,presented to the public as a very normal way of expressing beliefs.An intelligent person will alway...\n\nQ: What's the best tide for this passage?", "options": ["How to help children make use of the Internet?", "Why is the Internet so useful in our life?", "Should people stop using the Internet?", "Should the Internet be censored?"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2250, "question": "Experts say that students usually need eight to ten hours' sleep at night, but most Chinese students do not get enough sleep. Some Chinese parents are usually glad to see their children study late. They will think their children work very hard. But not all parents are happy about this. Once a mother told us that every morning her 10-year-old boy put up one finger with his eyes still closed, begging for one more minute to sleep. Like thousands of students \"early birds\" in China, he has to get up before six every morning. A report shows that without a good night's sleep, students seem to be weaker than they should be. Many students have fallen asleep during class at one time or another. Too much homework is not the only reason why students stay up late. Some watch TV or play the computer gam...\n\nQ: According to the experts, students should   _  .", "options": ["develop good study habits", "work hard", "go to school before six", "come home late"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 21, "question": "Today, whether or not you follow the latest trends, one's fashion and choice of dress is a reflection of one's individual style and tastes. Can you still remember how you dressed at the start of China's opening-up? Today's program is one of a special series commemorating the 30th anniversary of reform and opening-up in China. In these two episodes we focused on fashion and style and were honored to invite two special guests to join us in studio--Ms. Zhang Ling from Raffles-BICT Inter-national College and Alex from Esquire magazine. When we talk about fashion, color is absolutely crucial. A color can reflect the mood of an individual person or the spiritual temperament of entire society or age. Mrs. Zhang and Alex talked about the colors which have left the greatest impression on them. In t...\n\nQ: All of the following EXCEPT   _   are keywords in representing the fashion of our generation.", "options": ["traditional brands", "international brands", "personal dress", "special stories"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 65, "question": "New research at Washington University School of Medicine in St. Louis shows that people who struggle with mood problems or addiction can safely quit smoking and that kicking the habit is associated with improved mental health. Cavazos-Rehg, an assistant professor of psychiatry, found that quitting or significantly cutting back on cigarette smoking was linked to improved mental health outcomes. Quitting altogether or reducing by half the number of cigarettes smoked daily was associated with lower risk for mood disorders like depression, as well as a lower likelihood of alcohol and drug problems. \"We don't know if their mental health improves first and then they are more motivated to quit smoking or if quitting smoking leads to an improvement in mental health,\" Cavazos-Rehg said. \"But either...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from this passage that   _  .", "options": ["Having quit smoking, tobacco addicts won't have the same problems again.", "About half of the daily smokers die from deadly mental diseases.", "More than 35,000 people were surveyed, 4,800 of whom were daily smokers.", "Quitting smoking may help avoid alcohol and drug problems."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3109, "question": "In the 1960s, people asked about your astrological sign . In the 1990s, they wanted to know your website. These days, having a web address is almost as important as a street address. Your website is an electronic meeting place for your family, friends and potentially, millions of people around the world. Best of all, you may not have to spend a cent. The Web is filled with all kinds of free services and all it takes is some time and creativity. Think of your home page as the starting point of your website. Like the table of contents of a book or a magazine, the home page is the front door. Your site can have one or more pages, depending on how you design it. While web pages vary greatly in their design and content, most use a traditional magazine layout. At the top of the page is a banner ...\n\nQ: According to the writer, your website is a place   _  .", "options": ["where you can meet people all around the world", "where you can buy what you want", "where you can get free services", "where you can meet people on the Internet"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 836, "question": "Scholarship Application Tips in 2014 for college students *Before you apply 1. Work hard to get good grades. Don't sweat about one bad grade, but always strive to do your best. 2. Get involved, and stay involved, in extracurricular activities. Sports, clubs, drama, bands and orchestras-these often count toward a student's overall scholarship application evaluation. The same goes for paid (or unpaid) work experience. 3. Begin your scholarship research early-by your sophomore or junior year of high school, if possible. Make special note of application deadlines, as they can vary from late summer to late spring. 4. Apply for as many scholarships as you are eligible for-several smaller scholarships can add up to a lot of money. *During the application process 1. Read the supplementary material...\n\nQ: Before you apply for a scholarship, it's best to  _  .", "options": ["pay more attention to grades than to extracurricular activities", "focus on only one scholarship application", "get as much work experience as possible", "begin your preparation as early as possible"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1447, "question": "Anyone who doubts that children are born with a healthy amount of ambition need spend only a few minutes with a baby eagerly learning to walk. No matter how many times the little ones stumble in their first efforts, most keep on trying, determined to master their amazing new skill. It is only several years later, many psychologists and teachers agree, that a good number of kids seem to lose their natural drive to succeed. For the parents of such kids, whose own ambition is often tied to their children's success, it can be a painful experience. Figuring out why _ is the first step. Assuming that a kid doesn't suffer from a learning disability, or isn't involved in some family crisis at home, many educators attribute a sudden lack of motivation to a fear of failure or classmate pressure. \"Ev...\n\nQ: We can infer from the passage that  _  .", "options": ["children who have lost their ambition will never succeed in life", "school performance has much to do with students' later success", "both the parents and the school are to blame for the lost ambition", "younger kids learning to walk are more ambitious than older ones"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 512, "question": "One day Mr. Brown sees a young woman in the street with children. He is very surprised because all the children are wearing the same clothes. White caps, blue coats and yellow trousers. \"Are all these children yours?\" he asks the woman. \"Yes, they are.\" she answers. \"Do you always dress them in the same clothes ?\" asks Mr. Brown. \"Yes,\" answers the mother. \"When we have four children, we dress them in the same clothes because we don't want to lose any of them. It is easy to see our children among other children because they are all wearing the same clothes. And now we have ten, we dress them like this because we don't want to take other children home by mistake. When there are other children among ours, it is easy to see them because their clothes are different....\n\nQ: Why does the woman dress her children in the same clothes? Because   _  .", "options": ["she has so many children", "she loves her children", "she doesn't want to take her children home", "she wants to see her children easily among others"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1616, "question": "Dear residents of Molten, We can't keep silent in the current wild situation when prices for all existing products are skyrocketing unbelievably. The enormous figures on price tags for food products have caused a real panic. We've perfectly realized that, and that's why we have kept bread prices affordable for all this time. At the moment all our reserves are exhausted. Stocks of bread-baking ingredients such as flour, sugar, butter and the like are running out. To buy what we need at reasonable prices is virtually impossible today. However, we all need bread every day, which means we will be forced to buy everything we need at much higher prices. The cost of bread closely depends on ingredients. Another financial crisis has led to a 300-percent increase of prices for butter, vegetable oil...\n\nQ: A possible solution to the crisis, what Figaro suggests is   _  .", "options": ["to use ingredients of a lower quality and lower energy prices", "to use shopping bags less", "to urge people to eat less bread", "to have the bread price raised to a certain level"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3270, "question": "If you have been joining in chat room conversations, or trading email with web pals , you have become one of the millions who write in a peculiarly short form of English. And you've got a sense of humor about short forms like SOHF (=\" sense\" of humor failure) to describe Internet newcomers who don't understand you. Across the globe, every night teenagers and their elders are \"talking online\", many of them all talking at the same time. It's fast: try talking to six people at once.It's brief: three or four words per exchange.It takes wit, concentration, and quick fingers. And it requires tremendous linguistic economy .There's neither time nor space for explanations.Why consume precious key-strokes telling six friends you have to leave for a moment to take care of your little brother when BRB...\n\nQ: In order to talk to several people at the same time on the Internet    _   .", "options": ["you have to speak fast and fluently", "you should speak with wit and humor", "you have to express your ideas in a brief way", "one should pay much attention to the accuracy of words"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1844, "question": "SYDNEY--Australia's economic boom is encouraging a steady stream of unexpected visitors looking for work: Americans. U.S. citizens are heading to Australia in small but growing numbers as near-10% unemployment at home drives more to look for jobs Down Under, where China's thirst for iron ore and energy is transforming the Pacific nation into an economic powerhouse. A bricklaying student from Silver Trowel, a leading provider of quality education and training in the building and construction industry, apprentices on a building project in Western Australia, where workers are in short supply. Daniel Davila, a 23-year-old floorer from Camarillo, California made the 14-hour move across the Pacific two years ago. He had been forced to take a job stocking shelves at a local grocery store for $8.9...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from the passage that 457 work visasare  _  .", "options": ["for skilled workers in some fields", "for students on the building project", "especially for American workers", "especially for those out of work"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3192, "question": "An American research company shows that $248.7 billion online sales are expected by 2014. It seems as if we can't get enough of spending money through countless online clicks today. Following are some of the incredible things that you can buy online! 1) Parents 51-year-old Michael Amatrudo from Connecticut put a posting on Craig list in 2009 to sell his elderly parents, asking for $155 in return. 2) Chewing Gum Bidding for Britney Spears' chewing gum reached $14,000 in 2004. The pop star's half-eaten sandwich also went for over $500. 3) Kidney Stone Star Trek actor William Shatner sold his kidney stone for $20,000 when he put it up for sale online to see how much a piece of him was worth. He ended up giving the money to charity. 4) An Imaginary Friend This imaginary guy went (or might stil...\n\nQ: What can be inferred from the text?", "options": ["Michael Amatrudo charged a high price for selling his elderly parents.", "William Shatner sold the kidney stone so as to donate the money to charity.", "Jon Malipieman was sold because he was not wanted any longer.", "The soul of Michael Jacobsen is worth more than that of Woody Allen."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1458, "question": "When, after a year of being alone on his island, Robinson Crusoe sees a footprint in the sand, the reader of Robinson Crusoe trembles. Will Crusoe find another human being to end his loneliness? Is the footprint the sign of an enemy? Since 1719, when Daniel Defoe wrote Robinson Crusoe, thousands of people who enjoy English novels have thrilled to this great adventure story. But few know how the story came to be written. Robinson Crusoe was the first English novel. Its birth brought together the misadventures of a Scotch \"failure\" and the untapped imagination of an aging English scribbler. Near the end of the Seventeenth Century, the hot-tempered Alexander Selkirk was charged with bad conduct while in church. Rather than face this charge, he ran away to sea. Several years later, Selkirk fou...\n\nQ: Daniel Defoe_.", "options": ["made his living as a writer", "got his start as a writer with the writing of Robinson Crusoe", "was very \"straight\"-he was hardworking and honest", "had little power of imagination, but succeeded with his novel because he worked hard"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 16, "question": "A girl with blue eyes is a blue-eyed girl. A man with long legs is a long-legged man. A woman with white hair is a white-haired woman. Children who have good looks are good-looking children. What do you do when you want to buy clothes? You go to a shop. If you can find clothes that are the right size for you, and if they are ready to wear, you will probably buy them. They are called ready-made clothes. If you can not find clothes that are the right size, you will go to a tailor's shop. A tailor is a man who makes clothes. He will measure you carefully and will then make clothes for you. Such clothes are called tailor-made clothes. What do we call a man who is dressed badly? We call him a badly-dressed man. A woman who is dressed well is called a well-dressed woman. What do you wear when it...\n\nQ: 56. If you come to England, bring both a raincoat and an umbrella because   _           .", "options": ["there is a lot of rain in England", "there are few umbrellas in the country", "gentlemen usually carry umbrellas with them in England", "walking with an umbrella in hand is popular in England"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 989, "question": "Traditionally, women have fallen behind men in adoption of Internet technologies, but a study released yesterday by the Pew Internet & American Life Project found that women under age 65 now get ahead of men in Internet usage, though only by a few percentage points. But the survey also noted that the _ between women and men on the Web is even greater among the 18-to-29 age group and African Americans. The report, \"How Women and Men Use the Internet\", examined use by both sexes, looking at what men and women are doing online as well as their rate of adopting new Web-based technologies. The report found that 86 percent of women aged 18 to 29 were online, compared with 80 percent of men in the same age group. Among African Americans, 60 percent of women are online, compared with 50 percent of...\n\nQ: In which age group do women fall behind men in the use of the Internet?", "options": ["18 to 29.", "Over 30.", "65 and older.", "Under 20."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 961, "question": "Finally, I entered the university. Because of my careful savings, I did not have to work during the school year. Then, summer came and it was time to work harder than ever. I continued working as a waitress at night, instructed tennis camps several mornings a week and worked as a secretary for a few hours in the afternoons. I even decided to take a class at a community college. This class at the community college saved me $650. It was an extremely tiring summer and made me anxious to return to my relatively easy life at the university. During my second and third years of undergraduate schooling, I decided to work about five hours per week in the campus admissions office answering phones. This provided a little spending money and kept me from drawing my savings out. The overall situation lo...\n\nQ: The passage is mainly about how the writer   _  .", "options": ["made money on the college campus", "managed to make full use of her vacation", "was forced to support herself by her mother", "was shaped by working parttime through college"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3466, "question": "Choosing the Right Resolution Millions of Americans began 2014 with the same resolution they started 2013 with, a goal of losing weight. However, setting weight loss as a goal is a mistake. To reach our goal of losing weight --- the output, we need to control what we eat --- the input ( ). That is, we tend to care about the output but not to control the input. This is a bad way to construce goals. The alternative is to focus your resolution on the input. Instead of resolving to lose weight, try an actionable resolution: \"I'll stop having desert for lunch,\" or \"I'll walk every day for 20 minutes.\" Creating a goal that focuses on a well-specified input will likely be more effective than concentrating on the outcome. Recently a new science behind incentives , including in education, has been ...\n\nQ: The writer strongly believes that we should   _   .", "options": ["develop good habits and focus on the outcome", "be optimistic about final goals and stick to them", "pick specific actions that can be turned into good habits", "set ambitious goals that can balance the input ang output"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2096, "question": "A newspaper reporter's job can be very interesting.He meets all types of people and lives quite a busy life.He is _ for news all the time,then after several years he may get a desk job,and life becomes a bit more settled.Let's look at his work a little more closely.In a day he may have to interview the prime minister of a foreign country, and the next day he may be writing about a football match.Sometimes he may be so busy that he hardly has any time to sleep.And at other times he may go on for days looking out for news materials yet return empty--handed. In the beginning,a reporter has to cover a very wide field.After the early years he becomes more specialized in his work.For example,he may finaliy be asked to write only on court cases or politics or sports.Some reporters may become so s...\n\nQ: Why did the men break the reporter's camera?", "options": ["The reporter took their picture.", "They did not like him at all.", "They were afraid of his camera.", "The camera was in the way."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3463, "question": "Choosing the Right Resolution Millions of Americans began 2014 with the same resolution they started 2013 with, a goal of losing weight. However, setting weight loss as a goal is a mistake. To reach our goal of losing weight --- the output, we need to control what we eat --- the input ( ). That is, we tend to care about the output but not to control the input. This is a bad way to construce goals. The alternative is to focus your resolution on the input. Instead of resolving to lose weight, try an actionable resolution: \"I'll stop having desert for lunch,\" or \"I'll walk every day for 20 minutes.\" Creating a goal that focuses on a well-specified input will likely be more effective than concentrating on the outcome. Recently a new science behind incentives , including in education, has been ...\n\nQ: The writer thinks that setting weight loss as a goal is a mistake because   _   .", "options": ["it is hard to achieve for most Americans", "it is focused too much on the result", "it is dependent on too many things", "it is based on actionable decisions"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 629, "question": "In the US and Britain, the slogan around colleges was \"Save water. Shower with a friend.\" Now, Wuhan University has come up with another system for the campus bathhouse. It charges students for the amount of time in a shower. Before entering the bathhouse, students pay for the amount of time they want in the shower with cash or their student ID card. The clock starts ticking the minute the tape is turned on. It pauses when a button is pressed for soap. An integrated circuit (IC) card reader at each tap shows the time. No money, no water. The benefits of the new system can be seen with the old system, which charged 1 Yuan for each person regardless of time in the shower. The university used about 320 tons of water daily under the old system, but only 160 tons now. Many students use the new ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following is NOT true?", "options": ["Students buy the time of their showers.", "The clock times the student's bathing except when the bather pauses for soap.", "If money runs out, there will be no water.", "Having finished bathing, the student has to pay for it."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2140, "question": "Many kids don't drink enough water daily, according to a new study. The study's lead author, Erica Kenney, at first planned to look into the amount of sugary drinks kids were drinking in schools. However, during her research she found that many kids were simply not drinking enough water. Kenney and her team examined data from a group of 4,000 children, aged 6 to19, between the years of 2009 and 2012. The data was taken from the National Health and Nutrition Survey,a study on the health of children in the United States conducted each year by the Center for Disease Control and Prevention.. While looking through the survey results, she noticed that more than half of the kids who took part in the study were dehydrated . Of' that group, boys were 76% more likely than girls not to have enough wa...\n\nQ: The text mainly tells us that many kids  _", "options": ["don ' t like drinking water", "prefer sugary drinks to water", "are at risk of health problems", "don ' t drink enough water daily"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1692, "question": "Have you got any wonderful plans for your coming winter vacation? Here are some wonderful films for you to kill time. _ Verona De Tessant (Maya Rudolph) and Burt Farlander (John Krasinski) are in their early thirties and struggling to meet daily needs and build fulfilling lives as an artist and a salesman. When they learn they will soon become parents, they are faced with the challenge of how and where to raise a child and build a happy family. With a baby on his way, the young couple, look at their lives and are puzzled about what they really want. _ Lynn was married to Pual, but they broke up and Lynn took their daughter Alice while Paul got their son Dylan. Years later, now Dylan is getting married, and Lynn is attending the wedding, with her younger son Elliot and Ben. Elliot is a drug...\n\nQ: This passage aims to   _", "options": ["make comments on films for a cinema", "recommend several films for fun", "introduce films for a film corporation", "advertise several films for a website"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2127, "question": "The management and staff are happy to welcome you and will do all they can to make your stay an enjoyable one. We hope you will find the following suggestions and information of use to you. MEAL TIMES Our overnight charge includes a continental-type breakfast. Breakfast: 7:30-9:30 a. m. Lunch: 12:00-2:00 p. m. Afternoon tea: 4:00-5:30 p. m. Dinner: 7:00-9:15 p. m. Meals can be served in rooms at a small extra charge. We regret that owing to staff arrangements, meals cannot be served outside these times. In exceptional circumstances please consult one of our receptionists in advance. Light refreshments, including tea, coffee, biscuits and sandwiches, can be served in rooms between 10:00 a. m. and 11:00 p. m. except during the meal times listed above. Cold drinks are available in the room re...\n\nQ: Meals can be served   _  .", "options": ["outside the room at 3:00 p. m.", "in the dining-room at 6:00 p. m.", "in the dining-room from 7:30 a. m. to 9:15 p. m.", "in rooms at 9:00 p. m."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 403, "question": "prefix = st1 /PITTSBURGH, Sept. 7 -- At 26, many people haven't even decided on a career. Luke Ravenstahl, cashing in on his family's political tradition, is already the mayor of Pittsburgh, the youngest mayor of any major city in the country. Although mayors elsewhere have been younger, Jeff Dunkel was 18 in 2001 when he was elected mayor of Mount Carbon, small towns inNew York, and elsewhere have also elected teenagers as mayors. But,Tallahassee, is the only other city with a population over 100,000 that has had a mayor as young as Mr. Ravenstahl. A supporter of Mr. Ravenstahl said concerns about Mr. Ravenstahl's age would _ once the city saw his work ethic. But now comes the hard part. As he strives to be taken seriously and take charge of a city only recently back from the brink of ban...\n\nQ: What kind of Challenges will not Luke Ravenstahl cope with?", "options": ["Distrust from his citizens", "pressure from other outstanding young majors", "economical standstill of his city", "decreasing population in his city"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 789, "question": "It was almost six years ago that my family and I waited for her at the airport. Unsure of what to expect and a little bitter about such an experience that my mother was forcing upon me, I had mixed feeling about the girl from Madrid. Today,after making many memories and discoveries, I couldn't be more thankful for what that experience taught me. My family had the privilege to host Teresa for several summers. I became fond of her cheerful chatter, constant laughter ,and addiction to online shopping. She seldom took my unkind jokes seriously and always gave it right back to me, making our relationship closer. She could go on talking for hours about the beach outside her house, her family and friends, and her life at her school. While several aspects were very similar to my life here, I was a...\n\nQ: The author expected to travel to Europe in order to  _   .", "options": ["develop the little Spanish", "inform people there of American culture", "improve the skills to communicate with Teresa", "have a better understanding of European culture"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 184, "question": "There are a number of different ways to study a language, each of which has advantages and disadvantages. You may find a combination of these is a best choice for you. If you can find a course in the language you want to learn in your country, this is quite a good way to study. A variety of courses are usually available, including part-time and full-time courses. If you look around, you can probably find a course that suits your needs. The main advantage of such courses is that you'll have a teacher to provide you with instructions, support and with whom to practice your language. You will also be studying with others who are at more or less the same level and you can exchange ideas with them and help one another. One choice is to study a language in a country where it's spoken. There are ...\n\nQ: Studying in your country has many advantages except that    _   .", "options": ["there are many courses to choose from", "you can study with others of the same level", "all the courses are free of charge", "the teacher can offer you instructions and practice"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3076, "question": "One summer day as I was heading to the teaching building I heard someone call my name. I turned around and I saw Philip ,a counselor at our admissions office , standing with another young man, Philip introduced me to him, Stephen, and reminded me that Stephen would be taking one of my classes. Stephen looked at me. With a somewhat painful expression, he asked if my class was going to be hard and if he would be able to pass. I introduced all the things that he would be expected to learn. As we talked, I saw Stephen's eyes getting big with fear. I told him to do all of his assignments, and to hand them in on time. Rather than being overwhelmed by all of the work, I told him the most successful students made a master calendar of all the assignments so they could plan their workload. As the fa...\n\nQ: According to Stephen's questions to the author, we know that Stephen  _  .", "options": ["wasn't very confident about himself.", "didn't want to attend the author's class.", "had never been an A student.", "couldn't pass the author's exam."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1181, "question": "Nowadays everybody seems to think that they know English. Many people speak it but few speak it really well. Practice is necessary in speaking English well. Reading is also one of the things that will help you to speak English better. Read whenever you can and whatever you like! Read papers and Internet sites that you like in English every day. Then, you will see that the number of known words is increasing and you are able to speak with more skills. Then you will have made the foundations and a good basis of English. It is not good to stop and get stuck there. Going to England or an English speaking country is a good choice, but many people cannot afford it. If you cannot go, reading and speaking with your friends will also help you to practice your English. However, I think that it is ve...\n\nQ: What does the writer suggest doing about reading?", "options": ["Trying to improve your vocabulary.", "Keeping on reading when you have time.", "Stopping when you have a good basis of English.", "Looking up every unknown word when reading."], "answer": 1}]